♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪When you say you love me♪
♪It's more than I ever imagined♪
♪Slowly♪
♪Stay by my side♪
♪Love is the warmth of everyday life♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪You lean your forehead against mine♪
♪Then you keep grinning like a fool♪
♪Little by little♪
♪You come closer to me♪
♪A warm love song plays in my ear♪
=The One=
=Episode 25=
Su Yan.
Cheng Lin's awake.
Really?
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪Waiting for an answer I'll never get♪
You're awake.
How do you feel?
Do you feel sick?
Does it hurt?
Anything else feel wrong?
Do you recognize me?
I'll get the doctor.
So you do care about me.
♪Your tenderness fades too soon♪
♪Like rain tinged with regret♪
♪I fold my longing into an old umbrella♪
♪But I can't escape the loneliness♪
I'm sorry.
I...
I'm the one who should be sorry.
This whole thing...
Ge Yao did it.
She was coming after me.
You got hurt because of me.
Why are you apologizing?
None of this was your fault.
If our places were reversed,
I... I don't know if I could've
♪You could say time would make it fade♪
protected you like you protected me.
Good.
If you're ever
forced to choose again,
choose yourself. Don't hesitate.
♪Pulled by the past
till my world fades out♪
Why are you so good to me?
♪Who says those fleeting moments♪
Because you're everything to me.
♪Can you hear how much I miss you?♪
♪It hits like a wave I can't contain♪
♪I can't let go of the path we shared♪
♪But you said time would make it fade♪
What are you doing?
You...
My phone.
How did you know
my passcode?
I memorized it.
♪Then goof off for the camera?♪
This one's good.
Post it.
Post what?
Post it on social media. Now.
Let everyone know
I'm
yours.
♪I listen to you♪
♪I follow your lead♪
♪Our friends all♪
♪Cheer for love♪
♪It's really here♪
♪Holding me tight♪
♪Leaving me flustered♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪When you say you love me♪
♪It's more than I ever imagined♪
♪Slowly♪
♪Stay by my side♪
♪Love is the warmth of everyday life♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪You lean your forehead against mine♪
♪Then you keep grinning like a fool♪
♪Little by little♪
♪You come closer to me♪
♪A warm love song plays in my ear♪
♪Why are you such a tease?♪
♪You tease me, then make it up to me♪
♪I make a wish on the sea breeze♪
♪And hear the waves confess♪
♪The tide carries our future home♪
♪Why does your shirt pocket♪
♪Always hold a few chocolates?♪
♪Without even trying♪
♪You melt♪
♪The emptiness in my palm♪
♪Love is really here♪
♪Holding me tight♪
♪Leaving me at a loss♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪When you say you love me♪
♪It's more than I ever imagined♪
♪Slowly♪
♪Stay by my side♪
♪Love is the warmth of everyday life♪
♪The way you move in slow motion♪
♪Makes me a little shy♪
♪You lean your forehead against mine♪
♪Then you keep grinning like a fool♪
♪Little by little♪
♪You come closer to me♪
♪A warm love song plays in my ear♪